-=The Last Fantasy=- 出品：TLF HalfCD Team  压制：20qq 本作品仅供交流学习，严禁商用
北京
Peiking has changed so fast.
베이징은 너무 빨리 변했다.[fix]
变得这么快
20年的功夫她已经成为一个现代化的城市
In 20 years, it's become a modern city.
20년 사이에, 그곳은 현대적 도시가 되버렸다.[fix]
我几乎从中找不到任何记忆里的东西
Almost nothing is as I remembered.
기억나는 것이라곤 거의 없다.[fix]
事实上这种变化已破坏了我的记忆
Change has wiped out my memorize.
변화가 내 기억을 지워버렸다.[fix]
我分不清幻觉和真实
I can't tell what's imagined from what's real.
내가 상상했던 일들과 실제로 일어났던 일들을  난 구별하지 못한다.[fix]
我的故事总是发生在夏天
My stories always take place in summer.
내 이야기는 항상 여름에 일어난다.[fix]
炎热的气候使人们裸露得更多
People expose more of themselves in the heat.
사람들은 햇빛에 몸을 드러내놓고,[fix]
也更难以掩饰心中的欲望
and find it harder to control their desires.
그들의 욕망을 통제하기가  어렵다는 것을 깨닫는다.[fix]
那时候好象永远是夏天
It seemed like it was always summer then.
그래서 이 이야기는  항상 여름에 일어났는지도 모르겠다.[fix]
太阳总是有空出来伴随着我
The sun always had time to come out and play with us.
태양은 항상 제 시간에 어김없이 나오고, 우리와 함께 어울린다.[fix]
阳光充足
The sunlight was so relentless,
햇빛은 아주 가차없었고,[fix]
太亮
so bright,
아주 밝았기 때문에[fix]
使得眼前一阵阵发黑
that our eyes were washed in waves of blackness.
우리의 눈은 어둠의 물결속에서만  씻겨질 수 있었다.[fix]
阳光灿烂的日子
In the Heat of the Sun.
햇빛 쏟아지던 날들.[fix]